[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the huge blue diamond from the 1997 movie Titanic?", "correct_answer": "Heart of the Ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue Heart", "Hope Diamond", "Eye of the Hurricane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Awarded with Best Picture from the Independent Spirit Awards, this drama is based on the murder of 14-year-old Marcy Renee Conrad.", "correct_answer": "Rivers Edge", "incorrect_answers": ["Drugstore Cowboy", "Stand By Me", "Blood Simple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The  protest march from Philadelphia to Teddy Roosevelts home in 1903 was called this.", "correct_answer": "The March of the Mill Children", "incorrect_answers": ["The March of the Veterans", "The March of the Unemployed", "The March of the Suffrajets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the maximum distance between Mars and the Sun?", "correct_answer": "249,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["500,000,000", "275,000,000", "327,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first female professor at Princeton University?", "correct_answer": "Hannah Arendt", "incorrect_answers": ["Rosalind Yalow", "Susan Sontag", "Mary Robertson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the dictionarys meaning of this meal: stuffed derma; roasted fowl intestines with a seasoned filling of matzo meal and suet.", "correct_answer": "Kishke", "incorrect_answers": ["Criadillas", "Limburger", "Lutefisk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Disney animated feature Bambi, after the mother is shot, Bambis father leads him away into the thicker parts of the woods. What is  the name of Bambis father?", "correct_answer": "The Prince of the Woods", "incorrect_answers": ["Redding", "The Stag", "The Alpha Stag"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which great film director began his career as an underwater camera operator for Jacques-Yves Cousteau?", "correct_answer": "Louis Malle", "incorrect_answers": ["Francois Truffaut", "Jean-Luc Godard", "Jean Charles Tacchella"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Take 50ml Rye Whiskey, 25ml Sweet Vermouth, 1 dash Angostura Bitters. Stir all the ingredients together with ice and strain in a martini glass. Garnish with a Maraschino cherry.", "correct_answer": "Manhattan", "incorrect_answers": ["Irish Coffee", "Grapefruit", "Jamaica Glow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these plants was believed to scare off vampires and keep them at bay?", "correct_answer": "Wild rose", "incorrect_answers": ["Hyacinth", "Dandelion", "Parsley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sweetened condensed whole milk is canned milk concentrate with molasses added to it.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Amethyst", "incorrect_answers": ["Narcissus", "Rose", "Daisy"]}]